London's favorite thief is all grown up.
Twist is a crime, drama, action film directed by Martin Owen.
A Dickens classic brought thrillingly up to date in the teeming heartland of modern London, where a
group of street smart young hustlers plan the heist of the century for the ultimate payday.
Oliver Twist, played by Raff Law.
Fagin, played by Michael Caine.
Sikes, played by Lena Headey.
Red, played by Sophie Simnett.
Dodge, played by Rita Ora.
Losberne, played by David Walliams.
Twist is a 2021 British crime drama film directed by Martin Owen and
co-produced by Noel Clarke and Jason Maza, who also stars in the film.
The film, based on the 2014 Tom Grass novel Twist which is itself an adaptation of Charles Dickens' 1838 novel
Oliver Twist, stars Raff Law, Michael Caine, Noel Clarke, Lena Headey, Rita Ora and Sophie Simnett.
Twist was released on Sky Cinema on 29 January 2021 and was
met with negative reception from critics.
The film explores themes of graffiti, parkour, art gallery, art theft.
The tone is emotional and intense.